http://www.chessbase.com/pages/legal

We use cookies and comparable technologies to provide certain functions, to improve the user experience and to offer interest-oriented content. Depending on their intended use, analysis cookies and marketing cookies may be used in addition to technically required cookies. Here you can make detailed settings or revoke your consent (if necessary partially) with effect for the future. Further information can be found in our data protection declaration.
Agree and continue
Pop-up for detailed settings
We use cookies and comparable technologies to provide certain functions, to improve the user experience and to offer interest-oriented content. Depending on their intended use, cookies may be used in addition to technically required cookies, analysis cookies and marketing cookies. You can decide which cookies to use by selecting the appropriate options below. Please note that your selection may affect the functionality of the service. Further information can be found in our privacy policy.
Technically required cookies
Technically required cookies: so that you can navigate and use the basic functions and store preferences.
Analysis Cookies
To help us determine how visitors interact with our website to improve the user experience.
Marketing-Cookies
To help us offer and evaluate relevant content and interesting and appropriate advertisement.
Save and continue
Shop
Home
OPENINGS A-Z
Support
ChessBase Magazine
FAQs
Contact us
SHOP
Search:
Language:
Search:
Language:
DE
EN
ES
FR
Language:
SHOP
english
deutsch
espanol
française
Imprint
ChessBase GmbH
Osterbekstr. 90a
22083 Hamburg
Germany
Privacy Policy
General
By visiting our website, data pertaining to your access (e.g. date, time, website requested, browser type used, IP address) may be collected on the server. The recording serves technical and statistical purposes.
If you leave comments, your IP address will be stored permanently. The recording is intended to warrant legal prosecution in case certain comments include illegal content.
To the extent further personal data (such as email addresses) are collected, we comply with the requirements of the German Federal Data Protection Act and the German Teleservices Act or use such personal data collected with your consent (e.g. when you send us a request).
Your personal data will only be transferred to third parties to the extent such transfer is required for the purposes of your request or you have consented. You may withdraw your consent at any time with effect for the future.
Our website uses cookies. These are small text files stored in your computer’s main memory. If you revisit our website the browser resends the cookie to the server. This allows us to improve your access to our site. You can prevent storage of cookies by choosing a disabling option in your browser settings. However, this may limit the functionality of our website as a result.
Google Analytics
Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service also referring to cookies. Google Analytics is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.
The information generated by the cookie is usually transmitted to a Google server in the United States and stored there. Your IP address, however, is previously truncated by Google within member states of the European Union or in other states which are party to the agreement on the European Economic Area. On our behalf, Google will use the transmitted information to evaluate your use of the website, compile reports about website activities, and provide us with further services related to website and Internet usage. The IP address sent from your browser as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with other data by Google.
You can prevent storage of cookies by appropriately setting your browser software. In addition, you can prevent data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of the website (including your IP address) from being collected and processed by Google by downloading and installing a browser plug-in from the following link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en. Alternatively, you can click on the following link: javascript:gaOptout(). In such case, an opt-out cookie will be set that hinders future collection of data by Google Analytics when visiting our website.
Facebook
Our website uses the social plugins provided by the social network facebook.com. The social network is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA.
The plugins are identified by respective Facebook logos or descriptions. If you visit a page containing such plugin, your browser sets up a connection to Facebook's servers. The content of the plugin will be transmitted to your browser directly from Facebook and will be implemented into our website. Therefore, we have no influence as to the specific data Facebook collects via the plugins. The following data are collected by Facebook according to our knowledge: By implementing the plugin, Facebook receives the information that a user visits the page. If you are logged in to your Facebook account Facebook can match your page visit to your account. If you use the plugins, e.g. by clicking the "Like" button, the respective information is sent to Facebook and will be stored there. To the extent you are not a Facebook member, Facebook may still collect and store your IP address. According to Facebook's statement, only anonymized IP addresses will be stored in Germany.
Documentation regarding the purpose and scope of the data collection and use by Facebook as well as your rights and options to modify respective setting can be found at: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/.
Google+
Our website uses the "+1" button provided by the social network Google+. The social network is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.
If you visit a page containing such button, your browser sets up a connection to Google's servers. The content of the button will be transmitted to your browser directly from Google and will be implemented into our website. Therefore, we have no influence as to the specific data Google collects via the button. According to Google's statement, no personal data will be collected by merely visiting the page. If you click to the button and you are logged in to your Google+ account, Google will collect and use data such as the IP address.
Documentation regarding the purpose and scope of the data collection and use by Google as well as your rights and options to modify respective setting can be found at: http://www.google.com/intl/de/+/policy/+1button.html.
Twitter
Our website uses the buttons provided by the online service Twitter. The service is operated by Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA.
If you visit a page containing such buttons, your browser sets up a connection to Twitter's servers. The content of the buttons will be transmitted to your browser directly from Twitter and will be implemented into our website. Therefore, we have no influence as to the specific data Twitter collects via the buttons. According to Twitter's statement, only the website's address and the user's IP address are collected and used for displaying the buttons.
Documentation regarding the purpose and scope of the data collection and use by Twitter as well as your rights and options to modify respective setting can be found at: http://twitter.com/privacy.
Deletion, Correction and Inquiries
We delete your personal data when the recording is no longer required for the purpose it was collected for or when the recording is in breach of legal requirements. You have the right to correction of incorrect personal data as well as blocking and deletion of your personal data to the extent no statutory obligation to preserve such data applies.
We are happy to provide information as to the personal data pertaining to you we have recorded. Please contact the address provided in the imprint of this website.
Online Dispute Resolution
Please note the platform for online dispute resolution as provided by the European Commission: http://ec.europa.eu/consumers/odr/. We are not obliged to participate in dispute resolution proceedings in front of a consumer arbitration board and are principally not willing to take part in such proceedings.
Privacy policy
|
Imprint
|
Contact
|
Home
© 2017 ChessBase GmbH | Osterbekstraße 90a | 22083 Hamburg | Germany
Still no ChessBase Account?
learn more >
8 million games online! Updated weekly, our definitive database has all the latest games.
With Live Book and Let’s Check!
Still no ChessBase Account?
learn more >
My Games – Access your games from everywhere. Store your games, training material and opening repertoire in the cloud. Annotate, analyze and share.
Still no ChessBase Account?
learn more >
Sac, sac, mate! Solve tactical positions of your playing strength. Boost your calculation skills. Enjoy adrenalin rush with tactic fights!
Still no ChessBase Account?
learn more >
Thousands of hours of high class video training. Openings, Middlegame, Endgame Lessons.
Top authors like Daniel King, Lawrence Trent and Rustam Kasimdzhanov
Still no ChessBase Account?
learn more >
Real Fun against a Chess Program! Play, analyze and train online against Fritz. Beginner, club and master levels. Assisted play and calculation training.
Still no ChessBase Account?
learn more >
Learn openings the right way! Build and maintain your repertoire. Memorize it easily move by move by playing against the variation trainer.
Still no ChessBase Account?
learn more >
The ultimate chess experience every day, PlayChess.com welcomes 20,000 chess players from all around the world – from beginner to grandmaster.
ONLINE SHOP
Realizing an Advantage
In this DVD the author answers how to realize an advantage, considering both the psychological aspects of the realisation of an advantage and the technical methods.
€29.90
Advertising
Books, boards, sets:
Chess Niggemann
Books, boards, sets:
Chess Niggemann
